In this clip I'm going to show you a great resource on the internet for your family and it's called iGoogle.
So we go to the internet and we type in www.igoogle.com.
They have set up a web page that you can customize to your own and then save it and put a password on it so you and your family can access it.
Once we're here we're going to go to make it your own.
So we're going to click on that and now it's going to let us decide what we want on our google page on our iGoogle.
I would like the calendar and I like the weather, but for my kids I don't want all the news popping up, because some of that is not child friendly.
But I do want to add bookmarks and this is going to let us save our kids websites, links to their websites on this page.
Once I have clicked on what I do want and don't want, I click show my page.
Now, our page is very basic here, but it just has a place for us to add bookmarks, has a our calendar and our weather.
We also can add a page for our child where they can add different games and things to their page as well.
Once we have this all customized and set up the way we want it, this would be a good page to save as your homepage so that your child is direct to this page every time they get on the internet.